In this section we're going to be discussing a model known as 123s of customer service.
In this section we're going to discuss the model known as the 123s of customer service.
Now it is just a model meant to help you remember the different types of customer service and what is important as far as following those steps.
The one in customer service is to remember to deal with only one customer at a time.
It doesn't matter what customer just came before or what customer your anticipating will come next or whatever distractions maybe going around you.
It's most important to remember that when you're dealing with a customer that is only your customer at that time.
The two customer service is a two way exchange.
Now it's not always just all about the customer wants but you have some input or to make any of that experience great for the customer as well.
So remember two way exchange we will discuss all of these a little bit more detail.
The three solve or identify your customers issue within three minutes now is that a hard and fast rule, no but it is a very good guideline.
When you put together the 123s of customer service you will be providing great customer service for him or her.